[Applause]
I'd like to talk a little bit about the
war in the Persian Gulf doin's in the
Persian Gulf you know my favorite part
of that war it's the first war we ever
had that was on every channel plus cable
and the war got good ratings too didn't
it got good ratings well we like war we
like war we're a warlike people we like
war because we're good at it you know
why we're good at it because we get a
lot of practice this country's only 200
years old and already we've had 10 major
Wars we average a major war every 20
years in this country so we're good at
it and it's a good thing we are we're
not very good at anything else anymore
can't build a decent car can't make a TV
set or a VCR we're at the fuck got no
steel industry left can't educate our
young people can't get healthcare to our
old people but we can bomb the shit out
of your country all right
especially if your country is full of
brown people oh we like that don't we
that's our hobby that's our new job in
the world bombing ground people Iraq
Panama Grenada Libya you got some brown
people in your country tell them to
watch the fuck out or we'll goddamn bomb
them but when's the last white people
you can remember that we bombed can you
remember the last white can you remember
any white people we've ever bombed the
Germans those are the only ones and
that's only because they were trying to
cut in on our action they wanted to
dominate the world bullshit that's our
fucking job now we only bomb brown
people not because they're trying to cut
in on our action just because they're
brown now you probably noticed I don't
feel about that war the way we were told
we were supposed to feel about that war
the way we were ordered and instructed
by the United States government to feel
about that war you see I tell you my
mind doesn't work that way I got this
real moron thing I do it's called
thinking and I'm not a very good
American because I like to form my own
opinions
I don't just roll
/ when I'm told to sad to say most
Americans just roll over on command not
me I have certain rules I live by my
first rule I don't believe anything the
government tells me nothing and I don't
take very seriously the media or the
press in this country who in the case of
the Persian Gulf War were nothing more
than unpaid employees of the Department
of Defense and who most of the time most
of the time function is kind of an
unofficial public relations agency for
the United States government so I don't
listen to them I don't really believe in
my country and I gotta tell you folks I
don't get all choked up about yellow
ribbons and American flags I consider
them I consider them to be symbols and I
leave symbols to the symbol minded I
look at war a little bit differently
to me war is a lot of prick waving okay
simple thing that's all it is war is a
whole lot of men standing out in the
field waving their pricks at one another
men are insecure about the size of their
dicks and so they have to kill one
another over the idea
that's what all that asshole Jacques
bullshit is all about that's what all
that adolescent macho male posturing and
strutting in bars and locker rooms is
all about
it's called dick fear men are terrified
that their tricks are inadequate and so
they have to compete with one another to
feel better about themselves and since
war is the ultimate competition
basically men are killing each other in
order to improve their self-esteem you
don't have to be a historian or a
political scientist to see the bigger
dick foreign policy theory at work it
sounds like this what they have bigger
dicks bomb them and of course the bombs
and the rockets and the bullets are all
shaped like dicks it's a subconscious
need to project the penis into other
people's affairs it's called fucking
with paper
[Applause]
so
as far as I'm concerned that whole thing
the Persian Gulf was nothing more than a
big prick waving dick fight in this
particular case Saddam Hussein had
questioned the size of George Bush's
dick George Bush had been called a wimp
for so long
wimp rhymes with limb George has been
called a wimp for so long that he has to
act out his manhood fantasies by sending
other people's children to die even the
name Bush even the name Bush is related
to the genitals without being the
genitals of course is a sort of passive
secondary sex characteristic now if this
man's name had been George Boehner well
he might have felt a little bit better
about himself and we wouldn't have any
trouble over there in the first place
this whole country has a manhood problem
big manhood problem in the USA you can
tell from the language we use language
always gives you away what did we do
wrong in Vietnam we pulled out not a
very manly thing to do is it when you're
fuckin people you got to stay in there
and fuck them good fuck
fuck them to death stay in there and
keep fucking them until they're all dead
we left a few women and children alive
in Vietnam and we haven't felt good
about ourselves since that's why in the
Persian Gulf George Bush had to say this
will not be another Vietnam he actually
used these words he said this time we're
going all the way imagine an American
president using the sexual slang of a
thirteen-year-old to describe his
foreign policy if you want to know what
happened in the Persian Gulf just
remember the names of the two men who
were running that war Dick Cheney and
colon Powell somebody got fucked in the
ass hurt me about due to start bombing
some small country that only has a
marginally effective Air Force seems to
me like we're weeks overdue to drop high
explosives on helpless civilians people
who have no argument with us whatsoever
I think we ought to be out there doing
what we do best gang making large holes
in other people's countries I hate to be
repetitious but we are a warlike lot we
can't stand it not to be fucking with
somebody we couldn't wait for that cold
war to be over could we couldn't wait
for the Cold War to be over so we can go
and play with that ties in the sand go
and play with our toys in the sand and
when we're not invading some sovereign
nation or setting it on fire from the
air which is more fun for our Nintendo
pilots then then we're usually declaring
war on something here at home
ship a notice that about us we love to
declare war on things here in America
anything we don't like about ourselves
we declare war on it we don't do
anything about it we just declare war on